♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
This doesn't come off easily.
[grunting]
Could it be I left it there?
Is this what you're looking for?
[screaming]
[gasping]
Maybe you should go to the wake tomorrow.
[Atoy] I suspect
what happened to Tonet wasn't an accident.
What do you mean?
Because I went back to the place
where she died.
[Atoy] I found a piece of evidence
that might have been left behind.
[indistinct chattering]
[in English] This is
my sister-in-law, Martina,
and her son, Gavin.
[in English] My condolences.
[Atoy] Ah, sorry, I just
got distracted by your bag.
But it seems to be missing
one stud, like… this?
[in English] Um,
I'm just gonna get a drink.
[in English] Excuse me.
Where were you all day yesterday?
Were you at a mall?
The same mall where Tonet
had the accident?
- You killed my sister?!
- [in English] Let me go!
[Emerson] You killed my sister?!
- [Martina, in English] Let me go!
- [Emerson] Huh!? Do it!
How dare you!
Did you come here just to make sure
that my sister was killed?!
I came here
to respectfully offer condolences!
[in English] And then, you're gonna
accuse me of such things?!
- [in English] Enough!
- You're not family!
[in English] She's accusing me of killing
some girl that I don't even know!
Because killing isn't new to this family!
It's like we never did anything right!
[Red] Let it go.
What's important
is we know what Atoy is thinking.
[in English] So, what are you gonna do?
That evidence… We need to divert it.
PREVIOUSLY
[music fades]
Bro…
Are you okay?
[muffled chattering in the distance]
I saw it in her eyes.
She really looked guilty.
[pensive music playing]
Even so,
you still shouldn't have strangled her.
She could sue you for that.
I'm serious. I'll really
file a case against her.
Based on your evidence.
Bro…
That's a bit unclear.
It's still not enough evidence.
What I find even more puzzling,
is that if it's true, what's her motive?
We'll find out once she's investigated.
I'll get help from my lawyer client.
[Emerson] 'Toy…
If things get messy,
whose side are you on?
[suspicious music playing]
The mother of your child
is from that Regalia family.
Theirs or mine?
I don't want us to clash again.
As long as we're on the right side.
[music fades]
Just don't leave me hanging, okay?
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[music swells]
[electronic blipping]
[Dmitri] Do you fairly believe that
Martina is guilty of that girl's death,
based only on Atoy's
informal investigation?
Dad, you know Atoy.
He's a tracker.
[in English] He knows what he's doing.
[in English] That's true.
But we both know
that Atoy is biased against Red
because they fought before.
What if he just made a mistake?
What if he's just looking
for someone to blame
to appease the family of the deceased?
[in English] Look.
[in English] They're not perfect.
[in English] But you're too hard
on Red and Martina.
Martina did everything
she could to find your child.
She already apologized
to you for all her mistakes.
Now, if she's guilty,
I won't side with her.
[in English] But you have to give her
the benefit of the doubt.
After all, she's still your family.
So, please, believe her innocence first.
[pensive music playing]
[clears throat]
[in English] Hi, Ms. Audrey!
Ria here, secretary of Ma'am Martina.
We have a breakfast meeting.
[in English] Ah, okay.
Uh, Martina will be out in a while.
[suspicious music playing]
It's just the two of us here.
Be honest with me.
Where were you really yesterday?
[in English] I was at my office!
At Bahay Kayakap!
Ria, right?
Yes.
Um, was Martina
at the office the other day?
[in English] Around 12 p.m. onwards?
Yes, ma'am.
[dramatic sting]
Uh, are you sure?
As in you saw her?
Yes, ma'am.
Actually, she even asked me to buy lunch.
I have a picture…
You can see her in the background.
Here.
- Is there more?
- Yes, ma'am.
- [dramatic sting]
- [tense music playing]
Ah, ma'am, I'll just prepare
my presentation.
Oh-- Okay, okay.
Thank you.
[helper] Ma'am?
Ma'am, excuse me.
I saw this under the console table
when I was cleaning.
I don't know what it's for.
Ah-- Okay, okay.
[helper] Okay, ma'am.
[tense sinister music playing]
What's that?
[in English] Bag stud.
Like the one from Martina's bag.
Let me see.
Is this the bag stud she lost?
Does this look like
the one Atoy saw at the mall?
Ah, sir, maybe I should be the one
to give it to Ma'am Martina.
[music fades]
[in English] I think Martina deserves
an apology from you.
[dramatic sting]
[siren blaring]
[muffled chattering in the distance]
[pensive music playing]
How's Emerson?
[Atoy] Mmm.
You, how are you?
Have you spoken to Martina?
So, Emerson is really
going to file a case.
You know, at first,
I really thought Martina was involved.
That's why I didn't defend her
when you all ganged up on her.
[in English] But now,
I really think I was wrong.
[somber music playing]
- How can you say that?
- Because…
When Tonet had the accident,
Martina was in the office
with her secretary.
I saw some pictures.
And that stud you found…
[in English] I don't think it was hers.
Because our maid found a stud at home.
I feel like Martina's bag stud
came off at home, not at the mall.
[suspicious music playing]
And I feel so bad because…
I confronted Martina.
I insinuated that
she was a killer.
[in English] But now,
it looks like she's innocent.
[music fades]
Are you sure she believed
I was at the office?
Of course, ma'am.
I even showed the selfie,
with you busy at work in the background.
[in English] That's the magic of AI.
- [in English] See?
- [in English] Very good, Ria.
[dramatic sting]
Ma'am, don't forget
my salary increase, okay? You promised.
Of course!
As long as you're loyal to me.
By the way, ma'am…
Was that bag stud we found yours?
- Has Audrey seen this?
- [Ria] Yes.
She even stared at it closely.
[suspicious music playing]
Nanny.
[helper] Ma'am?
Do you remember my favorite bag
with those metal designs?
One of them came off.
If you see it, please tell me,
or you can give it to Audrey
if you can't find me.
Yes, ma'am.
[in English] Thank you.
[music swells]
[in English] I'm such a freaking genius.
Audrey will swallow
everything she said to me.
[in English] Oh my gosh.
[music fades]
This is what you saw
at the scene of the accident, right?
[in English] Yes, Attorney.
Oh, that matches what
we saw Martina carrying,
so she can't deny it.
[in English] Okay. Highly suggestive,
but it does not rise to the level
of establishing criminal liability.
- [in English] Okay.
- [in English] Suspicion alone
is insufficient.
Without clear and convincing
proof of intent and unlawful conduct,
no crime can be legally imputed.
[pensive music playing]
What?
Emerson, you can file
a case against Martina Regalia,
but it's very unlikely you'll win.
Unless there's an eyewitness
or you can prove
that the perfume Atoy smelled
and this bag stud
are exclusively Martina's.
Because, look.
There are many bags
that have studs like this.
What should I do?
Emerson, I don't want you to suffer,
and if you ask me,
I would advise against it.
[dramatic sting]
[in English] Filing without solid grounds
risks an immediate dismissal.
You could even face unnecessary costs
and even counterclaims.
Looks like Attorney is right, 'Son.
Looks like we were wrong
to accuse Martina.
So that's it?
[sniffs]
[Emerson] So that's it, 'Toy?
[scoffs]
I wish you hadn't told me.
I wish you hadn't told me your suspicions.
So, I wouldn't have hoped for nothing.
[epic music playing]
'Son.
[in English] Boss.
Boss Red already gave an order.
Find out if Emerson
will file a case against his wife.
Boss, if Emerson pushes through
with his complaint,
what will happen to him?
He'll just lose.
But Boss Red is brutal when he's angry.
Emerson might end up like his sister.
[tense music playing]
He's bound to lose anyway.
So, why does something
have to happen to him?
Why do you have so many opinions?
Did anyone ask you?
Just follow orders!
Sorry.
[music fades]
[Emerson] How am I supposed
to eat all of this?
[somber music playing]
This is your fault too.
It's your fault,
because if I hadn't planned
to eat lechon that day,
maybe Tonet wouldn't
have been at the mall.
Maybe she'd still be here with me now.
[sighs]
[gentle music playing]
[Atoy] 'Son?
There's no Emerson here.
Ah, looks like there really isn't.
Looks like my cheerful friend is gone.
My handsome friend,
who's not too grumpy.
Oh.
This is the receipt from the coffee shop.
[pensive music playing]
[Atoy grunts] I paid for it
because you walked out.
Hey, pay me back, okay.
This is so expensive.
[Atoy] Oh?
That's not expensive at all.
What would you rather pay for? That?
It's more expensive
if you cover the attorney's fees.
That's a lot too.
It looks like you don't stand
a chance in that case, bro.
I thought we were going
to fight this, bro?
[suspicious music playing]
Bro…
Nothing.
Our evidence against Martina is weak.
The evidence is her bag and her perfume.
I spoke with Audrey.
[music fades]
She said…
Martina was really
at the office when it happened.
They have evidence.
She wasn't at the mall.
[pensive music playing]
And about the bag stud,
they found one at their home.
Bro…
Bro, I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
I miscalculated, bro.
Looks like we really have to accept
that what happened
to your sister was an accident.
[tapping on table]
Emerson…
Atoy has a point.
You know, we don't really know
why that happened to your sister.
[melancholic music playing]
But I'm sure
she wouldn't want you to be angry
at someone who's actually innocent.
[sighs]
[clicks tongue]
It's my fault too.
But I can't accept that it's my fault--
[sighs]
Eh--
Brother--
I was her brother, bro.
I'm the brother.
[sobs]
Wasn't I supposed to be
the one protecting her?
You both know that.
[sobs]
You know that!
Well, bro--
I was there.
I wasn't able to do anything, bro!
- Emerson--
- [Emerson inhales]
And now, I'm just looking
for someone to blame!
Bro, even the lechon,
I want to put the blame on it!
Stop blaming yourself. Come on.
[sighs]
[Atoy] 'Son…
'Son, just think about how lucky
you were to be with her.
It's a good thing
you reconciled with your sister.
That's true.
Thank you.
Thank you, really.
It feels like you're my brothers here.
[chuckles]
I love you guys. It's just not obvious.
[chuckles softly]
Thank you.
'Toy, thank you.
[deep breath]
You're my brothers now.
We even look alike.
I just look better by two showers, but…
[giggles]
- [Paldo] There you go.
- Thank you. Thank you, bro. Thank you.
[music fades]
If I didn't know these clothes
belonged to Tonet,
I'd think they were yours.
You're almost the same size as Tonet.
That's not my style, Mom.
And some of those she bought,
she said I'd wear them someday.
You know…
With Sis Tonet, I really felt
how nice it is to have a sister.
- [gentle music playing]
- [Cita inhales]
Isn't it like
Atoy has become your brother?
But, it's still different
having a sister, Mom.
Everything you want to say,
you can really tell her.
Brother Atoy is there too.
But it feels like
his world is different now.
He already has a child
and an adopted daughter.
Oh, Noel? I thought
you were coming home tomorrow?
We got laid off from work!
But it's fine.
I'm tired of being a helper.
So, what's your plan now?
[pensive music playing]
Nothing.
Rest, relax.
Well, the money you earn
from Atoy is enough, right?
And we still have a boarder upstairs.
Well, just raise her rent.
She's gone.
Damn her then!
She left?!
She hasn't even paid last month's rent!
She's dead.
Unbelievable.
How unlucky can you get, huh?
Karla, buy me some beer.
Three beers, okay!
Cita, give her money to buy.
Huh?
Money to buy beers!
Give her money. Are you deaf?!
[unsettling music playing]
[mumbling] For beer…
This is all I have…
How much--
Can you hurry up?
Are you just going to stare at each other?
That should be enough, here.
[tense music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
Martina, um…
I told nanny…
to return to you the stud she found.
I just wanted to check if…
you've received the bag stud?
[in English] I did.
Imagine, it was just here at home.
So that rock stud Atoy found at the mall,
whose could it be?
[in English] I guess we'll never know.
[in English] I also…
want to apologize.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] For what?
[in English] For accusing me
of killing Tonet,
or for being so hateful
towards me and your brother?
[in English] You know, Audrey…
we don't need to get along.
But do know that I always have your back,
because…
we're family, right?
[in English] Don't get me wrong, Martina.
But just because we're family
doesn't mean I'll side with what's wrong.
[in English] Noted
with many thanks, Audrey.
[Janine gasping] Mommy, Mommy!
Oh my… My dear?
Oh, why are you crying?
I dreamed of Tonet. She was angry at me.
[in English] It was just a dream, my dear.
It's not true that Tonet
is angry at you, okay?
Um, do you want to sleep in the room?
We'll sleep together.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] You know, Audrey, I think
Baby Janine needs a little bit
of a breather from all this…
trauma?
[in English] Maybe some fresh air
would do her some good.
Just the two of you, some…
mommy-daughter bonding.
[in English] What do you think?
[sniffles]
Mommy, let's just go on vacation.
And my birthday is coming soon.
Let's celebrate there instead?
[in English] Okay, dear. Yes.
[in English] Um, wherever you wanna go.
Come on, let's go to the room, baby, okay?
Don't cry anymore.
[tense music playing]
[electronic blipping]
- Ouch.
- What the hell?!
Why are you angry?
You're the one who bumped into me.
Hey, I do fight with kids, okay.
[Leon] Don't test me!
[Ibyang] Oh, so--
- Tatoy, I'll row, okay!
- [Atoy, indistinct]
Did you forget
your birthday gift to me, Ibyang?
What's that?
Um, she said she won't join
the boating activity anymore.
UP NEXT
[Audrey squeals]
[Audrey] My scarf!
- Mommy--
- [Audrey squeals]
[Janine] Mommy!
[water splashes]
Audrey?
Mommy!
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
- Audrey!
- ♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias